streamskill.com 2017-10-11

# Stream Skill Privacy Policy | Stream Skill

## 

**_P_** ** _rivacy Policy_**

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE OR OUR SERVICE. Simon Sez IT, Inc. (“Simon Sez IT”) and **_StreamSkill.com_** (“the Website”) (collectively “we”) are committed to protecting the privacy and security of our visitors, registered users, and subscribers who access our Website or Services). This Privacy Policy sets forth how the Website and our Service collect and use personal information. By using the Website and Service, you acknowledge that you have read and accepted our privacy practices set forth below. 

If you do not accept our privacy practices, then you should not continue to use either the Website or the Service. This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into and forms part of our Terms of Service. 

**1.** **Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information** ****

We have implemented commercially reasonable security measures and follow generally accepted industry standards to protect personally identifiable information sent to our Website or provided to our Services, both during transmission and afterwards. It is your responsibility to ensure that you do not disclose your password to anyone. 

However, despite our efforts to maintain the confidentiality and security of your account, no method of transmission over the Internet and no method of electronic storage is completely secure. Although we make every effort to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**2.** **Personal Information We Will Collect** ****

When you register an account with us, we may collect personal information from you. You must provide your first and last name and email address. You will also be asked to create a password for your account, and we may collect the IP address of your computer. If you purchase a subscription, we will ask for your credit card information and billing address. 

We use “cookies,” which are small data files placed and stored on your computer, to help you manage your use of our Website and Service. Cookies are used as follows: 

(a) To recognize you as a regular user; 

(b) To remind us of who you are; 

(c) To estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Website and Service to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior; 

(d) To track your progress; 

(e) To measure traffic patterns for use as a research tool to understand how our users habits are similar or different from one another; and 

(f) To conduct other research. 

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, in order to give you the chance to determine whether or not to accept it. If you do not accept cookies, some pages of this Website or our Service may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information. 

**3.** **Purposes for Which We Will Use Personal Information**

We make every effort to identify the purposes for which we will collect personal information at or before the time the information is collected. We will use your personal information only for the purposes disclosed at the time of collection or as otherwise set out in this Privacy Policy, unless we have your consent for another use, or unless such other use is authorized or required by law. 

Our policy is to collect personal information from you for the following purposes: 

(a)to market and promote our Service; 

(b)to generate analytics for the improvement of the Website and Service, and for marketing purposes; 

(c) to maintain a commercial relationship with you and to communicate with you (which may include advertising, promotions, and account verification); 

(d) to identify your needs and/or preferences; 

(e) to meet legal and regulatory requirements; 

(f) to administer, maintain, manage, and improve our business operations; and 

(g) as otherwise required by law. 

**4.** **Sharing of Personal Information**

We do not rent, trade, or share personal information with third parties, except to provide products or services which you requested when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

(a) We may share your personal information third parties for our shopping cart and merchant processing functions, which parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes; 

(b) We may share your personal information third parties to send out our newsletter; 

(c) We may share aggregate personal information with third party search engines for the purpose of conducting analytics; 

(d) We may share your personal information with third party consultants and developers; 

(e) We may share your personal information with affiliates; 

(f) We may share your personal information if required by law and if we believe that the disclosure is required or necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial processing or legal process served on our Website or Service; 

(g) We may share personal information if we believe that it is required in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, a potential threat to the physical safety of a third party, or as otherwise required by law; 

(h) We may transfer personal information to a third party entity in the event of an assignment of this Website or the Service for any reason. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of personal information; 

(i) We may share personal information with our legal, financial, and other professional advisors; or 

(j) We may share personal information with third parties upon receiving your consent as required by law. 

Except as provided above, we will not share any of your information to any third party without permission. 

**5.** **Access to Your Personal Information** ****

You can review, update, delete, or correct your personal information on file with us online or in person at any time. To access your personal information, we require a written request; unless you login and update your personal information yourself directly. Upon receipt of any written request, we will take commercially reasonable steps to provide you with the opportunity to access any such information. You should send any written requests to us at **support@streamskill** **.com**. 

**6\. Email Requests for Personal Information**

We will never initiate a request for personal information by email or pop-up window. If you receive a request by email or pop-up window, please do not respond and notify us as set forth below. 

If you ever believe that you have been a victim of fraud, please report it to the police and take all available actions to protect yourself. Also, please notify us, so that we can take all possible actions to protect you and the other visitors, registered users, and subscribers. 

**7.** **Children** ****

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. In furtherance of this commitment, we restrict the use of our Website and Service to persons eighteen (18) years of age or older. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). 

**8.** **Contact with You**

We may use your email address to contact you from time to time, in order to send notices required by law, to provide information regarding this Website or our Service, or to resolve any complaint or suspicious transactions. You may at any time choose to unsubscribe (or “opt-out”) of any of our mailings, either by adjusting your membership settings or by contacting us at **support@streamskill.com**. 

**9.** **Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy** ****

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time at our sole discretion and without prior notice. You should check back with us from time to time in order to confirm that there have been no significant changes. 

Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy then in effect at the time of use. 

**10.** **Other Legal Notices** ****

If you ever have a dispute over privacy or security, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. We will always make every effort to resolve any concerns that you have regarding privacy that arises in connection with this Privacy Policy. 

**11.** **California Users** ****

If you are a California resident, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of your personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing uses. California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to us at our email address in order to receive information on the categories of customer information that we shared and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year. To obtain this information, please send an email message to **support@streamskill.com** with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you in your email address in response. 

Please be advised that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response. ****

**12.** **International Users** ****

If you are accessing this Website or Service from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website or Service, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy as incorporated into our Terms of Service, you will be transferring your personal information into the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

**13.** **Contact Us** ****

If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy or if you need further information regarding the access to your personal information, or how your personal information is used, you may contact us at **support@streamskill.com**. 

**14\. E** **ffective Date**

This Privacy Policy was last modified on the **11** th of August, 2016\.
